http://www.educationaltoysplanet.com/privacypolicy1.html

Educational  Toys Planet
Search SHOP BY AGE0 to 12 month12 to 24 months2 years3 years4 years5 years6 years7 years8 years9 years10+ yearsCATEGORYActivity ToysBuilding ToysScience ToysArts & CraftsElectronic LearningRole PlayingPuzzlesGamesActivity BooksEducational KitsOutdoor Play & SportsToy VehiclesMusical ToysPlaysets & FiguresPlay FoodBaby PlayBath ToysParty FavorsSKILLSCognitive DevelopmentCreativityManipulative SkillsImaginationLanguage ArtsLearn to ThinkLife SkillsMathMusicPhysical DevelopmentScienceSocial SkillsSocial StudiesBRANDSTEACHER STORESALE Home > Customer Service > Privacy Policy
>   Privacy PolicyEducational Toys Planet takes your privacy seriously. We really care about keeping all the personal information that Educational Toys Planet collects and receives, private and secure. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.Secure Shopping You can feel safe when you shop with Educational Toys Planet! The e-commerce service is powered by Yahoo!, one of most trusted names on the Internet and a leading provider of e-commerce services. PayPal verification increases the security of the PayPal network. Verified members have successfully completed PayPal's verification system to establish their identity with PayPal. We utilize Secure Socket Layering (SSL) technology to encrypt your personal and financial information, including the credit card number, while it is transmitted over the internet between your computer and our website's servers. SSL is the industry standard technology for secure online transactions. Encryption is a advanced method of scrambling data.Email Privacy During checkout you may choose the option to receive our offers and updates by checking the appropriate box below your e-mail information window. Educational Toys Planet will not send you any promotions by electronic (as well as regular) mail unless you request such service. Want to unsubscribe from our e-mailed promotions? If you have subscribed the e-mail promotional updates, you may unsubscribe at any time. Please contact us to unsubscribe, or click “unsubscribe” on our e-mailed promotional offer. See our Privacy Policy for more information.What personal information is collected? Educational Toys Planet obtains personal information when you purchase from Educational Toys Planet online store to complete your transaction. When you shop we may ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, billing address, PayPal account information, etc. Educational Toys Planet automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. We may also acquire personal information about other people from you when you order toys or gift certificates to be shipped to your special child. If you register your e-mail address on our website, we will collect this information on our secure server.How do you use the information you collect? We use information for the following general purposes: * to processing and fulfill your requests for products and services * to contact you about the status of your order * to respond to your customer service request or inquiry * to send you notifications about important product recalls * to customize the advertising and content you see * to notify you about special promotions, or programs – upon your request only * to invite you to review the purchased toys * to conduct research in order to improve our servicesSharing and Disclosure Educational Toys Planet does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or companies except to provide products or services you have requested. If you request such services (for example, from the toy manufacturer, regarding the toy exchange issue, or parts replacement), we officially require that the companies observe the same privacy policy for our customers, as we guarantee on this page.E-mails You will not receive any promotions by electronic (as well as regular) mail until you request such service registering on our website or during checkout. We will e-mail you the information about our promotional updates only if you registered for such service on our website, or requested it by checking the appropriate box during checkout. Want to unsubscribe our e-mailed promotions? If you have subscribed the e-mail promotional updates, you may unsubscribe at any time. Please contact us to unsubscribe, or click “unsubscribe” on our e-mailed promotional offer.Confidentiality and Safeguarding We limit access to personal information about you to employees who, we believe, reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! Google and others to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! or Google may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, click here. Cookies are a common name for small files stored by your internet browser on your computer. Cookies allow expediting the checkout and improving your shopping experience. We can set Educational Toys Planet cookies on your computer if you choose to accept cookies. Cookies let us to recognize our customers and securely keep the information you provided about yourself. Your information is stored on our secured database. Your credit personal or credit card information is never stored within one of our cookies.Children’s Privacy We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 on Educational Toys Planet. We will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission.Misuse of Personal Data If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 732-414-2184 or via email at help@edutoysplanet.com.Policy Changes We may change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions through this website. This policy has been revised as of March 20, 2018. 0-12 Mon 1 Year 2 Years 3 Years 4 Years 5 Years 6 Years 7 Years 8 Years 9 Years 10+ YearsHelpContactAboutBlogPrivacy Receive Coupons and Special Promotions:
FacebookTwitterPinterest
We may earn a commission for purchases made through our links.Copyright © 2020 Educational Toys Planet LLC. All Rights Reserved.
